

- daniil.volosyuk@gmail.com
- danyavol.dev

CONTACT

- t.me/d4nvol
- linkedin.com/in/danyavol
- github.com/danyavol



JavaScript Type

TypeScript Angular

React Vue

HTML CSS SASS/SCSS

Less

ApexCharts

Angular Material

Bootstrap

Taiga UI

Bulma

Google Charts

Semantic UI

Husky pre-commit

RxJS NgRx

TFS

Docker

Webpack

Redux

Jasmine

Jest

Git

Karma

Ionic

Capacitor

Azure DevOps

TeamCity

Heroku

GitHub Actions

Firebase

Netlify

Figma

Google Play Console

BitBucket

GitLab Jira

Railway

i18n

Google Analytics

Node.js

Hotjar

Express

Newrelic

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

JWT

mongoose

cheerio

DANIL VOLOSYUK

Senior Frontend Engineer

My experience at the web development is 4 years. I have large experience in web application development, including creating the architecture of the client and server sides, configuring builds, pipelines and deploying apps to cloud services.

Besides that, I think soft skills are just as important as hard skills. Therefore, I am open to feedback and always try to be a good team member. Also can call myself a fast-growing, responsible and multi-tasking person.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2021 - current



Frontend Engineer

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - MINSK, WARSAW

Client project (Under NDA)

The project is about cloud services, security, datacenters, giving servers in rent, physical access to datacenters. Also it has 3 sub-projects and I worked there, too.

- Migrated pages from Angular.js to Angular 9
- Developed, tested and deployed features, fixed bugs
- Refactored existing forms and pages
- Worked with forms, charts, widgets
- Analyzed and improved app performance, bundled size reduction
- Updated Angular version from 9 to 14
- Performed code review
- Created designs of new components and new features, suggested UI and UX improvements (we didn't have designers in the team)
- Set up Angular library with shared components across client sub-projects
- Worked with CI in TeamCity, configured build pipelines in Azure DevOps, configured restrictions for Pull Requests, branches security
- Conducted demo of new features to the client, organized knowledge transfer meetings for Coherent team and for client team
- Clarified requirements
- Participated in daily meetings with client

Have used such technologies as: Typescript, Angular.js,
Angular 9-14, Git, TFS, Azure DevOps, TeamCity, RxJs,
ApexCharts, Google Charts, Google Maps, Angular Material,
ESLint, Jasmine, Karma, Quill

Internal projects

Worked on two internal company projects.

Tools, Environment, Languages and Technologies: TypeScript, Angular, NgRx, RxJs, Jira

Oct 2020 -Feb 2021

Frontend Developer

PRIVATE CLIENT FROM CANADA

Developed a front-end part of the control panel of the company to be used by employees (add/edit products, contacts, events; statistics, dashboards, etc.) and helped a little bit with back-end part.

jQuery, HTML, CSS, JS, Front (Bootstrap 4 based template), Java, Spring.

2019 - 2022

Freelance

Periodically I helped people who I know or people from freelance platforms to fix their issues or build apps for money. Some of the apps are presented on my personal page.

I have used different technologies, including SQL/NoSQL databases, Node.js, Java, JavaScript, Angular, React, Vue, jQuery and many others related frameworks and libraries.

2018-current

Personal Projects

Besides the work I got paid for, I have a lot of fun and useful personal projects, some of them have become really successful. I got a lot of knowledge and experience from it, highly recommend to visit my personal page (https://danyavol.dev) and check the most remarkable projects.

EDUCATION

Dec 2023

Security Testing Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Jun 2023

Node.js

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Mar 2023

React Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Apr 2021

Angular Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Feb 2019 -Dec 2019

Frontend Developer Courses

IT ACADEMY STEP - MINSK

During the course I have learned all basic technologies needed to apply for Junior Frontend position and a little bit more. Also learned basics of Angular and React frameworks.

2018 - 2022

Bachelor's Degree

INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY MITSO

Specialization - Information systems and technologies



- English (B2 Level)
- Russian (Native)
- Belarusian (Native)
- Polish (A1 Level)